<audio_item>
  <dc.identifier.other>87250-SR-37-1-1</dc.identifier.other>
  <dc.title>Sound Recording - University of Michigan Men's Glee Club &amp; Northwestern University Glee Club Joint Concert - 1966 November 12</dc.title>
  <dc.contributor.author>University of Michigan. Men's Glee Club</dc.contributor.author>
  <dc.data.issued>2015</dc.data.issued>
  <dc.date.created>11/01/2013</dc.date.created>
  <dc.coverage.temporal>1966 November 12</dc.coverage.temporal>
  <dc.type>Musical performances</dc.type>
  <dc.rights.access>This material is available for research only in the Reading Room of the Bentley Historical Library at the University of Michigan (Ann Arbor, MI).</dc.rights.access>
  <dc.rights.copyright>This recording may be protected by copyright law. Every audio, visual, or textual work has copyright protection unless that protection has expired over time or its creator has placed it in the public domain. It is the responsibility of anyone interested in reproducing, broadcasting or publishing content from the Bentley Historical Library collections to determine copyright holders and secure permissions accordingly.</dc.rights.copyright>
  <dc.date.open>2015</dc.date.open>
  <dc.description>Content note: The sound recording(s) associated with this repository item derive from a single audio reel tape. A single tape may yield multiple audio files if there were variations in tape stock, speed, or channels (i.e. stereo or mono). For more information see http://deepblue.lib.umich.edu/handle/2027.42/108126.</dc.description>
  <dc.abstract>[Program 37] : [Side 1] : [Part 1] : Tape 1 of 2; The Northwestern University Glee Club performs: Now Let Every Tongue Adore Thee; Art Thou With Me; Zion Hears The Watchmen Singing; Habanera; The Testament of Freedom, I. The God Who Gave Us Life, III. We Fight No For Glory, IV. I Shall No Die Without Hope; Those Broadway Gals: Mame; - Jerry Herman, Gigi (Gigi), Frederick Loewe, Dolly (Hello, Dolly); The University of MichiganPresentation to Alumni of outstanding achievement awards by President Harlan Hatcher (9:30 p.m. concert). The Michigan Men's Glee Club; Laudes Atque carmina; Dona Nobis Pacem; Chorus of the Returning Pilgrims; Lord Randall; My Good Ol' Man; Stomp Your Foot; The Bugler's Holiday; It's a Grand Night for Singing; If There is Someone Lovelier Than You; Who; All the Things You Are; I Know That You Know; Good Night Sweetheart; Some Enchanted Evening; I Got Rhythm. Selections of Michigan songs by The Friars. Combined Glee Clubs perform Alma Maters - Hail Northwestern; The Yellow and Blue.</dc.abstract>
  <bitstream>
    <dc.title.filename>87250-SR-37-1-1-am.wav</dc.title.filename>
    <dc.description.filename>[Program 37] : [Side 1] : [Part 1]</dc.description.filename>
    <dc.format.mimetype>audio/wav</dc.format.mimetype>
  </bitstream>
  <bitstream>
    <dc.title.filename>87250-SR-37-1-1-pm.wav</dc.title.filename>
    <dc.description.filename>[Program 37] : [Side 1] : [Part 1]</dc.description.filename>
    <dc.format.mimetype>audio/wav</dc.format.mimetype>
  </bitstream>
  <bitstream>
    <dc.title.filename>87250-SR-37-1-1.mp3</dc.title.filename>
    <dc.description.filename>[Program 37] : [Side 1] : [Part 1]</dc.description.filename>
    <dc.format.mimetype>audio/mpeg3</dc.format.mimetype>
  </bitstream>
  <bitstream>
    <dc.title.filename>87250-SR-37-1-1-001.jpg</dc.title.filename>
    <dc.description.filename>Item Photo</dc.description.filename>
    <dc.format.mimetype>image/jpeg</dc.format.mimetype>
  </bitstream>
  <bitstream>
    <dc.title.filename>87250-SR-37-1-1-002.jpg</dc.title.filename>
    <dc.description.filename>Item Photo</dc.description.filename>
    <dc.format.mimetype>image/jpeg</dc.format.mimetype>
  </bitstream>
  <bitstream>
    <dc.title.filename>87250-SR-37-1-1-003.jpg</dc.title.filename>
    <dc.description.filename>Item Photo</dc.description.filename>
    <dc.format.mimetype>image/jpeg</dc.format.mimetype>
  </bitstream>
  <bitstream>
    <dc.title.filename>87250-SR-37-1-1-004.jpg</dc.title.filename>
    <dc.description.filename>Item Photo</dc.description.filename>
    <dc.format.mimetype>image/jpeg</dc.format.mimetype>
  </bitstream>
  <bitstream>
    <dc.title.filename>87250-SR-37-1-1-005.jpg</dc.title.filename>
    <dc.description.filename>Item Photo</dc.description.filename>
    <dc.format.mimetype>image/jpeg</dc.format.mimetype>
  </bitstream>
  <bitstream>
    <dc.title.filename>87250-SR-37-1-1-notes.txt</dc.title.filename>
    <dc.description.filename>Item Notes</dc.description.filename>
    <dc.format.mimetype>text/plain</dc.format.mimetype>
  </bitstream>
  <bitstream>
    <dc.title.filename>87250-SR-37-1-1.xml</dc.title.filename>
    <dc.description.filename>METS XML</dc.description.filename>
    <dc.format.mimetype>text/xml</dc.format.mimetype>
  </bitstream>
</audio_item>
