<audio_item>
  <dc.identifier.other>95107-SR-1-1</dc.identifier.other>
  <dc.title>Sound Recording - Michigan Lumberjacks, Stories, Songs, Instrumentals - 1965 May</dc.title>
  <dc.contributor.author>Welliver, Harry B.</dc.contributor.author>
  <dc.data.issued>2015</dc.data.issued>
  <dc.date.created>6/24/2013</dc.date.created>
  <dc.coverage.temporal>1965 May</dc.coverage.temporal>
  <dc.type>Oral Histories</dc.type>
  <dc.type>Musical performances</dc.type>
  <dc.rights.access>This material is available for research only in the Reading Room of the Bentley Historical Library at the University of Michigan (Ann Arbor, MI).</dc.rights.access>
  <dc.rights.copyright>This recording may be protected by copyright law. Every audio, visual, or textual work has copyright protection unless that protection has expired over time or its creator has placed it in the public domain. It is the responsibility of anyone interested in reproducing, broadcasting or publishing content from the Bentley Historical Library collections to determine copyright holders and secure permissions accordingly.</dc.rights.copyright>
  <dc.date.open>2015</dc.date.open>
  <dc.description>Content note: The sound recording(s) associated with this repository item derive from a single audio reel tape. A single tape may yield multiple audio files if there were variations in tape stock, speed, or channels (i.e. stereo or mono). For more information see http://deepblue.lib.umich.edu/handle/2027.42/108126.</dc.description>
  <dc.abstract>[Side 1] : [Part 1] : No. 1 of 5; Performance by the Michigan Lumberjacks; George "Swede" Hedquist; E.C. "Doc" Beck; Don Baker; Leon May; Bob McFarlane; Frank Hubbard; Margaret L. Newell, pianist. From discs made approximately 1935. 1. Joe's Favorite (Instrumental) "The Lumberjacks, Who are They?" (talk, E.C. Beck Joe's Favorite (Instrumental), 2. Once More A Lumbering Go (Michigan Lumberjacks), 3. Down by the Wild Mustard River (Michigan Lumberjacks) (Story about Johnny Stiles) The County Fair Polka (Instrumental, Michigan Lumberjacks), 4. Fireman's Dance (Instrumental, Michigan Lumberjacks with Frank Hubbard, fiddler, Breckenridge, 86 years old when recorded) Old Pacific No. 2 (Instrumental, Michigan Lumberjacks with dulcimer solo by Don Baker of Ithaca; Peek-A-Boo (Instrumental, Michigan Lumberjacks with dulcimer solo by Don Baker of Ithaca, 5. Young Monroe (Vocal solo), 6. Paul Bunyan Tale (George "Swede" Hedquist, Detroit), 7. Pete Bateese (Talk by), 8. La Bon Louis and My Love is But a Lassie (Instrumental, Michigan Lumberjacks , 9. Jack Haggerty and His Flat River Girl (Leon Hay, Swede Hedquist and Bob McFarlane, with Margaret L. Newell, pianist), 10. Pine River Quadrille: Kitchen Sweat (Instrumental, Leon May Swede Hedquist, Margaret L. Newell, pianist), 11. When We a Lumbering Go (Vocal, Leon May, Bob McFarlane and Swede Hedquist, Margaret L. Newell, pianist) Note: The words peculiarly refer to "the Saginaw River Valley."</dc.abstract>
  <bitstream>
    <dc.title.filename>95107-SR-1-1-am.wav</dc.title.filename>
    <dc.description.filename>[Side 1] : [Part 1]</dc.description.filename>
    <dc.format.mimetype>audio/wav</dc.format.mimetype>
  </bitstream>
  <bitstream>
    <dc.title.filename>95107-SR-1-1-pm.wav</dc.title.filename>
    <dc.description.filename>[Side 1] : [Part 1]</dc.description.filename>
    <dc.format.mimetype>audio/wav</dc.format.mimetype>
  </bitstream>
  <bitstream>
    <dc.title.filename>95107-SR-1-1.mp3</dc.title.filename>
    <dc.description.filename>[Side 1] : [Part 1]</dc.description.filename>
    <dc.format.mimetype>audio/mpeg3</dc.format.mimetype>
  </bitstream>
  <bitstream>
    <dc.title.filename>95107-SR-1-1-001.jpg</dc.title.filename>
    <dc.description.filename>Item Photo</dc.description.filename>
    <dc.format.mimetype>image/jpeg</dc.format.mimetype>
  </bitstream>
  <bitstream>
    <dc.title.filename>95107-SR-1-1-002.jpg</dc.title.filename>
    <dc.description.filename>Item Photo</dc.description.filename>
    <dc.format.mimetype>image/jpeg</dc.format.mimetype>
  </bitstream>
  <bitstream>
    <dc.title.filename>95107-SR-1-1-003.jpg</dc.title.filename>
    <dc.description.filename>Item Photo</dc.description.filename>
    <dc.format.mimetype>image/jpeg</dc.format.mimetype>
  </bitstream>
  <bitstream>
    <dc.title.filename>95107-SR-1-1-004.jpg</dc.title.filename>
    <dc.description.filename>Item Photo</dc.description.filename>
    <dc.format.mimetype>image/jpeg</dc.format.mimetype>
  </bitstream>
  <bitstream>
    <dc.title.filename>95107-SR-1-1-notes.txt</dc.title.filename>
    <dc.description.filename>Item Notes</dc.description.filename>
    <dc.format.mimetype>text/plain</dc.format.mimetype>
  </bitstream>
  <bitstream>
    <dc.title.filename>95107-SR-1-1.xml</dc.title.filename>
    <dc.description.filename>METS XML</dc.description.filename>
    <dc.format.mimetype>text/xml</dc.format.mimetype>
  </bitstream>
</audio_item>
